Displays a message enhanced with escaped characters with several functions.

EECHO
	Feeds a new line (CR+LF). Equivalent to EECHO $n

EECHO message
	Displays the message that may have escaped characters. No advances
	automatically to a new line.

EECHO /?
	Displays this help.

Escaped characters:
	The messages may have escaped characters with special meanings. The escape
	character is '$'. Escaped characters arw case sensitive: $c is not the
	same as $C.

	The recognized escaped characters are as follows:
	$$
		Displays the escape character itself.

	$=character
		Changes the escape character. From here up to the end of the string
		or up to a new <escape character>=, "character"
		Permite modificar el caracter de escape. A partir de aquí hasta el
		final del mensaje o hasta un nuevo <caracter de escape>=, "caracter"
		will be the escape character instead of $.
		The following characters are not allowed as the escape one:
		^ | < > % # = [ { ( c C b g n r t

	$[[text]]
	${{text}}
	$((text))
		The text enclosed between double brackets, double braces or double
		parenthesis is not interpreted, it's displayed as is even with the
		presence of escaped characters.

	$#
		Ignores the rest of the line. Useful when the command is embedded in
		other commands (eg.: for) that can insert unwanted trailing spaces.

	$b
		Displays the backspace character. In the console, causes the cursor
		to move one position to the left.

	$g
		Displays the bell character. In the console, causes a sound to be
		played. More editor friendly that directly insert ^G.

	$n
		Feeds a new line (CR+LF). In the console, causes the advance to a new
		line.

	$r
		Displays a carriage return (CR). In the console, causes the cursor
		to be positioned to the beginning of the current line.

	$t
		Displays the horizontal tab character. In the console, causes the
		cursor to advance to the next horizontal tab.

	$c(JK|J.|.K)
		Modifies the color attributes of the characters that follow.
		J specifies the background color attribute and K specifies the
		foreground color attribute.
		J and K can be a hexadecimal digit from 0 to F denoting the color
		attribute or '.' denoting the color attribute remains unchanged.
		After execution of the command, the color attributes revert to those
		already established before execution.

	$C[+|-]posX[,[+|-]posY];
		Establece la posición del cursor. posX establece la posición
		horizontal y posY establece la posición vertical. posY es opcional y
		si no se especifica, la posición vertical del cursor queda inalterada.
		Si se especifica '+' o '-' delante de la posición, entonces ésta es
		relativa con respecto a la posición actual. Si no se especifica, la
		posición es absoluta.

Examples:
	EECHO $[[Hello World$]]$n
	- Shows 'Hello World$' (with no escape character interpretation) and feeds
	  a new line. It's the functional equivalent to echo Hello World$.

	for /f "tokens=1,2,3*" %%i in ('ver') do $EECHO $c.a%%i %%j $c.e%%k %%l$n
	- Shows 'Microsoft Windows' in bright green followed by
	  [Version x.xx.xxxx] in bright yellow. The background color remains
	  unaltered.

	for /l %%i in (10, -1, 0) do $EECHO $c4f%%i $r$# & choice /n /t 1 /s s > nul
	- Shows a 10 seconds countdown in red background and bright white foreground.

	EECHO $C8,+1;Hello$bsong$C1,-1;Result:$C+5,+1;i$n
	- Shows:
	   Result:
	          Hellsing

	EECHO One line$nAnother line$=@ $n Still in the same line@nAnother line @@
	- Shows:
	  One line
	  Another line $n Still in the same line
	  Another line @

	EECHO ${{There is no $c3a color change}},$c3a nut now it is
	- Shows: 'There is no $c3a color change,' with the current colors,
	  followed by ' but now it is' with cyan background and intense green
	  foreground.
 